<summary>
    <section id="a01">
        <title>01. Random Text Generator and SHA-256 Check</title>
        <description>
            This section introduces a tool that allows users to generate random text and compute its SHA-256 hash. Users can click a link to generate random text and subsequently compute its hash, with the result displayed in the designated area.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section id="a02">
        <title>02. Introduction to GitHub Code for Files</title>
        <description>
            This page serves as an introductory guide to a GitHub repository focused on file formats, including YAML, SQL, JSON, and CSV. It outlines the functionality and significance of each format, guiding users on how to navigate the repository and utilize the code provided.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section id="a03">
        <title>03. Speak To Your Friend</title>
        <description>
            This section provides various utilities including generating random hexadecimal values and random text. Users can specify the number of characters for both text and hex generation. Additionally, there are options for encrypting and decrypting text by entering the corresponding keys, as well as a clear function to reset all fields.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section id="a04">
        <title>04. Get Your YouTube Embed with Current Time Link</title>
        <description>
            In this part, users can embed a YouTube video and generate a link that includes the current playback time. Users can input a YouTube video URL, load the video, and copy a link that directs to the specific time. This section also includes a ciphered link feature with a tool to decipher Base64 encoded links.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section id="a05">
        <title>05. Duration Calculator and YAML Generator</title>
        <description>
            The Duration Calculator and YAML Generator is a simple web application designed to help users calculate the duration between two dates and generate a YAML configuration based on the input data. The tool allows users to input their name, a list of tasks, and start and end dates. It then calculates the number of days between the start and end dates and formats the information into a YAML format.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section id="a06">
        <title>06. Decipher Announcement / Cipher Text</title>
        <description>
            Provide a tool to decipher a ciphered announcement file and cipher plain text.
        </description>
    </section>
    <section id="a07">
        <title>07. I Ching Simulator</title>
        <description>
            Create a simulator for I Ching, explicitly stating that it has no connection to divinity or supernatural elements. The purpose of the I Ching simulator is to provide cues when people run out of ideas or wit, using the ancient Chinese text's wisdom and philosophy in a practical, secular manner.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a08">
        <title>08. Autocompete Dictionary</title>
        <description>
            Find your words here.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a09">
        <title>09. Get YouTube Embed with Time Link (Curtailed Start and End)</title>
        <description>
            This web tool allows users to generate a YouTube embed link with specific start and end times. Users can either load a video by providing a standard YouTube URL or by entering a custom embed URL with defined start and end times.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a10">
        <title>10. Generates a random series of keyboard characters distribution trying to be uniform</title>
        <description>
            Generates a random series of keyboard characters, appends them to a display, and plots a histogram of the character distribution. It will notify the user when the distribution is uniform.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a11">
        <title>11. Claim Verification Registry</title>
        <description>
            This tool computes SHA-256 hashes for input texts with appended random hex values and checks if the computed hash exists in a verification file, displaying the corresponding line if found in the record.
        </description>
    </section>


    <section id="a12">
        <title>12. File Cipher/Decipher</title>
        <description>
            This tool allows users to upload a file, cipher it with a provided or randomly generated AES key, and download the ciphered file as a12.ciphered.html. In another section, users can input an AES key to decipher the a12.ciphered.html file. If the key is correct, the decrypted announcement is displayed in an iframe within the page; otherwise, it announces an unauthorized attempt.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a13">
        <title>13. Distance Between Apples</title>
        <description>
            The provided code allows users to interactively move two red apple images on a map, displaying their coordinates and the distance between them in real time. As the apples are dragged, a line is drawn between them, with the distance shown both along the line and in the top-left corner. This solution offers a dynamic, visual way to measure and display the Euclidean distance between two draggable objects, with updates as the apples are repositioned.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a14">
        <title>14. Online Mnemonic Key Generator</title>
        <description>
            The online mnemonic key generator allows users to create and derive cryptographic keys based on a mnemonic phrase, which is a series of words commonly used for securely storing private keys. Users can input their own mnemonic words or generate a random set of words, and they are prompted to enter a password. The generator then uses the PBKDF2 key derivation function with SHA-256 to derive a secure key, ensuring the process is consistent with best practices in cryptography. The derived key, displayed in hexadecimal format, can be used for secure applications such as wallets or encryption systems.
        </description>
    </section>    

    <section id="a15">
        <title>15. Key Pair Generator</title>
        <description>
            Key pair generator with options for RSA, ECDSA, and EdDSA algorithms. It includes functionality for generating and exporting cryptographic key pairs, as well as generating test vectors with random bytes and signatures. The unit test section allows users to generate random bytes, create signatures using the private key, and verify the signatures with the public key, displaying results in real-time. Additionally, users can download or copy the generated test vectors. The unit test section is visually separated by 2 horizontal lines, and its functionality is placed before the test vectors mass generation section.
        </description>
    </section>    

    <section id="a16">
        <title>16. RSA/ECDSA Key Management and Signing</title>
        <description>
            Outlines a comprehensive tool for handling AES encryption and signing using ECDSA keys. Users can input their ECDSA private key in hexadecimal format, which is then encrypted using a randomly generated AES key. This AES key and the encrypted private key are displayed to the user, with options to copy to the clipboard or download. Additionally, users can load an encrypted private key file and input an AES key to decrypt it. The system verifies the correctness of the AES key by attempting to sign a message and verifying it with the public key. If successful, a timestamp is appended to the message in the format YYYY-MM-DD_HHmm_ss, and the user can input a text message to be signed. The signed message can also be copied to the clipboard or downloaded as a permit.signed.txt file. 
        </description>
    </section> 

    <section id="a17">
        <title>17. Web-Based Hex Key Derivation Tool</title>
        <description>
            This web-based tool allows users to input an initial hex key and specify a desired key length to generate a derived key using the PBKDF2 key derivation function with HMAC-SHA256. The tool provides an intuitive interface with input fields for the hex key and key length, a button to generate the derived key, and a feature to copy the derived key to the clipboard for convenience. Implemented with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, it utilizes the Web Crypto API for secure key derivation and conversion between hex strings and byte arrays.
        </description>
    </section>     

    <section id="a18">
        <title>18. Periodic Table Word Generator</title>
        <description>
            The Periodic Table Word Generator is an interactive web tool that converts a given input text into images of elements from the periodic table. Each letter in the word or phrase is mapped to the corresponding element's symbol (e.g., "H" for Hydrogen). For two-letter element symbols (e.g., "He" for Helium), the tool prioritizes combining two characters into an element symbol first, ensuring accurate matching. Special characters like spaces and punctuation remain as text. This tool provides an engaging and educational way to visualize text while learning about the elements of the periodic table.
        </description>
    </section>
    
    <section id="a19">
        <title>19. Website Playlist Manager</title>
        <description>
            The Website Playlist Manager allows users to upload, manage, and modify a list of URLs with optional descriptions. It enables functions such as reordering the list (up/down), removing items, and downloading the updated list in a specific format. The playlist can be loaded from `.txt` or `.json` files, and the list is saved in a `.txt` file with the format `[url][optional description]`. Each updated file is named with the current date and time to ensure uniqueness.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a20">
        <title>20. Hyperlink Maker</title>
        <description>
            The Hyperlink Maker allows users to upload a text file with URLs and optional descriptions in the format `[url][description]`. The tool generates HTML hyperlinks from the file's contents, displays them in an enumerated list, and provides a copy-to-clipboard functionality for easy copying of all generated links.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a21">
        <title>21. Status Code Display and Search</title>
        <description>
            The feature allows users to load a CSV file containing HTTP status codes, types, and meanings. It enables searching for a specific status code to display its type and meaning. Additionally, users can view the full list of status codes in a well-organized table format. This solution uses JavaScript to fetch the CSV content, parse it, and dynamically generate the table. The functionality includes buttons for loading data, searching by code, and displaying the full list.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a22">
        <title>22. Read and Display URL GitHub Raw Pages Content</title>
        <description>
            This page allows users to input a URL, fetch the content from that URL, and display it. After loading the content, a button is provided to remove all HTML tags from the fetched data, leaving only plain text. The user can load any page by entering its URL, and the page will be shown in a pre-formatted text block. The "Remove HTML Tags" button cleans the content by removing all HTML elements, providing a plain text version of the data.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a23">
        <title>23. Timeline</title>
        <description>
            This page creates a timeline section with animation effects using ScrollReveal.js. It includes several timeline items, each describing a significant event or milestone. The timeline items fade in from the left or right as the user scrolls, creating a dynamic and engaging visual experience. The design is responsive, adjusting the animation effects based on the screen size to ensure a seamless experience on both desktop and mobile devices.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a24">
        <title>24. 403 Access Not Granted</title>
        <description>
            This page creates a 403 Access Not Granted error page with a playful design featuring animations. It includes a keyhole and key SVG illustrations and a ghost animation that moves across the screen, revealing the message "You know you're supposed to leave, right?" The page is designed to provide a timeless, visually engaging experience on both desktop and mobile devices.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a25">
        <title>25. Interactive SVG Animation</title>
        <description>
            This page showcases an interactive SVG animation that generates colorful wave effects when the user clicks or touches anywhere on the screen. The page is designed to provide a seamless experience on both desktop and mobile devices, featuring a customizable SVG that animates based on user input. It includes dynamic elements like text, circles, and color transitions, all driven by JavaScript animations.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a26">
        <title>26. Tearable Cloth Simulation</title>
        <description>
            This page features an interactive tearable cloth simulation where users can manipulate the cloth with their mouse. The user can click and drag to tear the cloth, or right-click and drag to cut it. The simulation uses a canvas element to render the cloth, with physics-based interactions like gravity and user influence. The cloth is made of points connected by constraints, and tearing is enabled by removing constraints when the distance between points exceeds a threshold. Users can interact with the cloth in real-time, and additional information and links to the GitHub repository are provided for further exploration.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a27">
        <title>27. Interactive Skill Progress Bars</title>
        <description>
            This page displays interactive skill progress bars with animations for various technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, WordPress, Bootstrap, and Laravel. The bars animate their progress using CSS keyframes and JavaScript. Each skill's progress is displayed with percentage values that are dynamically updated by JavaScript, enhancing user experience with color transitions and smooth animations.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a28 to a38">
        <title>[28] to [38]</title>
        <description>
            This section includes interactive animations from a28 to a38. Refer to a40 for a tool that allows users to generate a list of URLs based on specified inputs. Users can input the root URL, path segments, file prefix, start and end numbers, choose whether to zero-pad the numbers, and select a file extension to create file traversal.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a39">
        <title>39. Error Status Code Search</title>
        <description>
            This page allows users to search for error status codes based on **Category**, **Code**, or **Description** from a CSV file. 
            The CSV data contains three fields: **Category**, **Code**, and **Description**. The user can load the CSV file, 
            perform dynamic searches, and filter results by **Category**. The page displays the matching results in a table format.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a40">
        <title>40. URL Traversal Generator</title>
        <description>
            This page allows users to generate a list of URLs based on specified inputs. Users can input the root URL, path segments, file prefix, start and end numbers, and choose whether to zero-pad the numbers and select a file extension. The generated URLs are displayed as clickable links.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a41">
        <title>41. Probability Finder</title>
        <description>
            This page allows users to input a percentage or adjust a temperature bar to find the closest equivalent probability of various events, such as getting struck by lightning, winning the lottery, or being born. It reads data from a CSV file containing probabilities of different occurrences.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a42">
        <title>42. Interactive Text Hyperlinking</title>
        <description>
            This page allows users to interactively select portions of text, create hyperlinks for them, and append them to the top of the page. The process starts with the user selecting a "start" point, followed by a valid "end" point, ensuring the "end" is after the "start". Once the selection is valid, a hyperlink is generated and displayed at the top. The selected text is also highlighted in the content box. The user can make multiple selections, with each new hyperlink being appended to the list, while previous selections remain highlighted. Invalid selections are rejected with a reset message. Additionally, users can download the page as an HTML file containing all selections.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a43">
        <title>43. Interactive Text Highlighting</title>
        <description>
            This page allows users to interactively select portions of text, highlight them in different colors from the selected text ranges.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a45">
        <title>45. YAML Highlighter</title>
        <description>
            This page allows users to upload a YAML file and highlight specified labels within the file content. Users can add multiple labels and choose different colors for each label to be highlighted. The YAML content is displayed with the selected labels highlighted in the chosen colors.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a46">
        <title>46. Node Connect Describe by YAML</title>
        <description>
            This page allows users to interactively create and connect nodes on a canvas. 
            Users can click to place nodes at random x, y coordinates and drag between nodes to establish connections. 
            The resulting connections are displayed in YAML format, detailing the start and end points of each connection.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a47">
        <title>47. Port and Description Lookup</title>
        <description>
            This page provides a dynamic lookup tool for ports and their descriptions. Users can enter a port number to see its corresponding description or type in a description to find matching port numbers. The page includes an autocomplete feature that suggests descriptions as users type, allowing for quick and easy lookup. The data is fetched from a CSV file containing protocol, port, and description information.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a48">
        <title>48. Summary of Emotional States and Reactions</title>
        <description>
            This page outlines various emotional states and reactions, categorizing them into clusters such as Surprise, Fear, and Joy/Happiness. It provides a detailed breakdown of emotions within each category, helping to understand the spectrum of human feelings and their nuances.
            Note: Also check a30.
        </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a49 to a50">
        <title>[49,50]. One-Time Pad Generator</title>
        <description>
            One-Time Pad Generator.
        </description>
    </section>
    
    <section id="a51">
      <title>51. Counter Crime Against Humanity: C2AH</title>
      <description>
        This page presents an interactive Sankey diagram that illustrates the relationships between various forms of harmful activities, including opinion manipulation, civil unrest, harassment, fraud, and others. It aims to visualize how these crimes interconnect and the impact they have on society. The goal is to raise awareness of these issues and foster a deeper understanding of how they spread and evolve over time. The Sankey diagram provides a visual representation of the flow between different harmful acts, allowing users to explore and understand their interdependencies.
      </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a52">
      <title>52. Cipher Utility</title>
      <description>
        Provide a tool to decipher a ciphered announcement file and cipher plain text.
      </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a53">
      <title>53. AES GCM Cipher Utility</title>
      <description>
        Provide a tool for AES GCM message ciphering.
      </description>
    </section>

    <section id="a54">
      <title>54. Configurable Security Options UI</title>
      <description>
        A web-based tool that dynamically loads security configurations from a `config.txt` file and presents them as categorized checkboxes. The interface organizes protocols, ciphers, hashes, and key exchanges into distinct sections with bordered boxes. Users can toggle options and submit their selections for display.
      </description>
    </section>    
      
    <section id="ax_summary">
        <title>Summary of All Pages</title>
        <description>
            The ax_summary provides an overarching overview of all the sections (a1 to a4). It synthesizes the key points and functionalities from each part, ensuring that users have a clear understanding of the tools and resources available across the different functionalities.
        </description>

    </section>
</summary>

